findfamilysupport.com 2019-07-05

# Find Family Support

Last Updated: March 1, 2018

Welcome to Find Family Support, a Web site ("Site").

We respect the privacy of those who access and/or use the Site ("you", "your", "user" or collectively "users") and are committed to protecting the personally identifiable information we collect. 

1\. **CHANGES TO THIS POLICY**  
If this Privacy Policy changes, we will post all changes in an amended version with a new "Last Updated" date at the top of this Privacy Policy. 

2\. **INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT**  
We collect two types of information from you. The first type is personal information that you actively choose to disclose ("Active Information") and the second type is anonymous aggregate information collected in a manner not visible to you or others visiting the Site ("Passive Information").

a. Active Information. Examples of personally identifiable information that you provide to us may include your first and last name, mailing address, email address, information about your finances, home ownership, education or interests. In providing Active Information, you consent and agree that we may us the information provided to present onsite advertising about third parties' products and services which are relevant to your stated interests. If you provide personally identifiable information to us, you may later elect to have that information kept from being used by us for marketing purposes. If you subscribe to our emails and newsletters, you may opt-out of receiving future mailings, by following the opt-out procedures set forth below. 

b. Passive Information. We record information relating to your use of the Site, such as the information you click on, your browser type, IP address, referring URL, and timestamp information. We use this type of information to administer the Site and provide the highest possible level of service to you. We may also use this information in the aggregate to perform statistical analyses of user behavior and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the Site. 

3\. **HOW COLLECTED INFORMATION IS USED**  
We do not share or disclose your Active and/or Passive Information with third party companies for their marketing purposes except as stated in this Privacy Policy, as otherwise permitted by law, or as authorized by you. We may employ third-party service providers to deliver emails on our behalf. In the event we use third party service providers, they are contractually required to maintain the confidentiality of our proprietary data, consistent with the terms and obligations described in this privacy policy. The information we collect allows us to keep you informed about industry developments, opportunities involving services and products, and relevant news and information. It also allows us to provide you with information about relevant government program requirements specific to your location, and custom services based on your personal interests, requests and needs. Finally, we may use your information for internal company purposes such as auditing, data analysis, research, information verification and anti-fraud activities. 

4\. **USE OF COOKIES**  
We use cookies to store users' preferences and to record session information, for purposes including ensuring that users are not repeatedly offered the same material and to customize any advertising and Web page content based on browser type and user profile information. Authorized third party advertisers on our site may employ cookies to track when and where you view or click on their advertisements and offers. They may collect and link your personally identifiable information, historical activities and Web usage from multiple sites. To learn more about this practice please click here: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp. You may disable cookies by adjusting the settings on your Web browser. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. Each browser is different, so you may wish to review the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. Note, however, that you may be required to enable cookies in order to use certain functions on our Site. We may also incorporate technologies used by advertising or analytical partners. Some such partners include, but are not limited to: (i) Google Analytics (used to track statistical information such as page visits and traffic source information allowing us to improve the performance and quality of the Site; to learn more about this please click here: http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html), and (ii) Google Advertising (used to track conversions from advertisements on the Google Search and Google Display Network; to learn more about this please click here: http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/). Third party pixels and content may also make use of cookies. We do not have access to or control over these third party cookies and this Privacy Policy does not cover the use of third party cookies. 

5\. **DO-NOT-TRACK POLICY**  
We honor "do-not-track" signals and therefore do not track individuals' online activities over time and across third party sites. However, while using our Site, third parties may collect users' personally identifiable information relating to their online activities while "do-not-track" technologies and similar mechanisms are activated. 

6\. **INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE**  
We do not share or disclose information we collect on our Site to third parties for marketing purposes except as stated in this Privacy Policy, as otherwise permitted by law, or as authorized by you. Third parties to whom we disclose information are required by law and contractual undertakings to keep your personally identifying information confidential and secure and to use and disclose for purposes that a reasonable person would consider appropriate in the circumstances, in compliance with all applicable legislation, which purposes are as follows: (i) to provide requested services to registered users on our behalf; and (ii) to send you more relevant advertising emails or offers for goods and services that may interest you. If these third parties wish to use your personally identifying information for any other purpose, they will have a legal obligation to notify you of this and, where required, to obtain your consent. If you do not want us to share your personally identifying information with third parties for the above-mentioned purposes, you may opt-out by following the opt-out procedures below. 

We reserve the unequivocal right to release all your information, to the maximum extent permitted by law in the event that: (i) we believe that the Site is being or has been used to commit unlawful acts, (ii) the information is subpoenaed or otherwise required in a court proceeding, (iii) you violate or breach an agreement with the Site, (iv) you have submitted fraudulent or otherwise invalid information to this Site, (v) we believe that you may harm, or have harmed, the property or other rights of us, our employees, the Site's other users or any other third party, (vi) we are sold to or otherwise acquired by any individual, entity or organization (i.e. to a successor entity in the event of sale of the business, including merger, bankruptcy or other ownership change), or (vii) when we otherwise deem it necessary or appropriate. We may disclose any record or communication to any third party when we, in our sole discretion, determine the disclosure to be appropriate including, without limitation, sharing your email address with other third parties for suppression purposes in compliance with the requirements of the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003, as amended from time to time, or any other applicable state or federal law, rule or regulation. 

7\. **OPTING-OUT**  
If you no longer wish to receive promotional communications from us, you may opt-out by following the instructions included in each promotional communication or by contacting us as provided in this Privacy Policy. You may continue to receive email communications from us for up to 10 business days from the time we receive your unsubscribe request. 

Please note that we can only control our own registered user list, email list, marketing practices, and policies. Third parties maintain their own mailing list, email list, marketing practices and policies. You will need to contact these parties directly in order to stop receiving communications from them. 

8\. **ACCESS/ACCURACY**  
To the extent that you do provide us with certain personally identifiable information, we strive to maintain the accuracy of this information. Our goal is to provide a means to contact us should you need to review, update or correct your information. If for any reason those means are unavailable or inaccessible through the Site, you may send your request to review, update or correct your personally identifiable information to legal@findfamilysupport.com and we will make reasonable efforts to comply as soon as possible. You must send your request from the email address you provided at the time of registration so we can uniquely identify you. All such requests are subject to execution of a release form that will be provided to you for this purpose. 

9\. **SECURITY OF INFORMATION**  
Use of the Site is at your own risk. We do, however, make reasonable efforts to secure your information, including, but not limited to, monitoring our network and data for intrusions. We also use industry-accepted standards to protect your information, including SSL encryption if transmitting sensitive information. Communications you may have with us via email or mail may not be secure unless we advise you that security measures are in place prior to your sending information. 

10\. **LINKS TO THIRD PARTY SITES**  
The Site may contain links to third party sites including sites with which we have no affiliation. We are not responsible for their privacy practices. It is recommended you read the privacy policies on all such third party sites. 

11\. **NO USERS UNDER 18; COPPA**  
If you are under 18, you may not access or use the Site. BY ACCESSING OR USING THE SITE, YOU REPRESENT THAT YOU ARE AT LEAST 18 YEARS OLD. In compliance with COPPA, we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from users under 13. 

12\. **NO INTERNATIONAL USERS**  
THE SITE AND SERVICES ARE NOT OFFERED FOR USE BY PERSONS RESIDING IN JURISDICTIONS OTHER THAN THE CONTINENTAL U.S. AND ALASKA AND HAWAII. If you live in any location other than the 50 states comprising the United States of America, you may not use the Site. 

13\. **CONSENT TO INTERNATIONAL TRANSFER**  
Information we collect may be transferred, stored or processed in any country that we or our affiliates, subsidiaries, third party service providers or agents maintain facilities. By using the Site or Services you consent to any such transfer, storage and processing of information. 

14\. **CONTACT INFORMATION**  
For more information, or if you have questions or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy or wish to opt-out as provided above, you may email us at legal@findfamilysupport.com.
